IWW Records 5210
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- I.W.W. "Evidence and Cross-Examination of J.T. (Red) Doran in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. Wm. D. Haywood et al." no publisher, 1918. 151 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom.., 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 2: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom.., 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Notes: Copy 3.
  - Item 4: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Notes: Copy 4.
  - Item 5: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Notes: Copy 5.
  - Item 6: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1946; Publication (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Notes: Copy 6.
- I.W.W. "The General Strike for Industrial Freedom." Chicago, 1933. 48 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 2: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom.., 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 5: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Item 6: The General Strike for Industrial Freedom., 1972; Publication (Box 11, Folder 17)
- I.W.W. "The General Strike for Industrial Freedom." Chicago, 1946. 48 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Gompers vs. Haywood., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Item 2: Gompers vs. Haywood., Publication (Box 11, Folder 18)
    Notes: Photocopy
- I.W.W. "Gompers vs. Haywood." Chicago, no date, 3 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Greatest Thing On Earth., Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: The Greatest Thing On Earth., Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: The Greatest Thing On Earth., Publication (Box 11, Folder 19)
- I.W.W. "The Greatest Thing on Earth." Chicago: I.W.W. Publishing Bureau, no date, 31 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The History of the I.W.W.: A Discussion of Its Main Features., 1923; Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Item 2: The History of the I.W.W.: A Discussion of Its Main Features., 1923; Publication (Box 11, Folder 20)
- I.W.W. "The History of the I.W.W." Chicago, no date. 31 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 21)
  Entry was struck out: missing?
- 'I.W.W. "The History of the I.W.W.: A Discussion of Its Main Features." Chicago: I.W.W., no date, 31 pages., Publication (Box 11, Folder 22)
  2 copies
- I.W.W. "Immediate Demands of the I.W.W." Chicago, no date, 14 pages, Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Immediate Demands of the I.W.W., Publication (Box 12, Folder 1)
- I.W.W. "The I.W.W. As Reorganized Under the Emergency Program: The Facts About the Split with Brief Review of Past History and Outline of the Present Situation." Chicago: I.W.W., 1925. 11 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The I.W.W. As Reorganized Under the Emergency Program: The Facts About The Split With Brief Review of Past History and Outline of the Present Situation., 1925; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: The I.W.W. As Reorganized Under the Emergency Program: The Facts About The Split With Brief Review of Past History and Outline of the Present Situation., 1925; Publication (Box 12, Folder 2)
- I.W.W. "The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice." 5th edition. Chicago: I.W.W. 1937. 124 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: 5th ed.
  - Item 2: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 4.
- I.W.W. "The I.W.W.: What It Is and What It Is Not." Chicago: I.W.W., no date, 39 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 7.
  - Item 2: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 8.
  - Item 3: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 5.
  - Item 4: The I.W.W. In Theory and Practice., 1937; Publication (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Notes: 5th ed. Copy 6.
- I.W.W. "Industry and Fraternity." Address by Sidney Strong. Chicago, I.W.W., 1917. 14 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  Missing
  - Item 1: The I.W.W.: What It Is and What It Is Not., Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The I.W.W.: What It Is and What It Is Not., Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The I.W.W.: What It Is and What It Is Not., Publication (Box 12, Folder 5)
- I.W.W. "The Lumber Industry and Its Workers." Chicago: I.W.W., no date. 91 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The I.W.W. Program., Publication (Box 12, Folder 6)
- I.W.W. "More Power To You." Chicago: I.W.W., no date, 43 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Industrial Unionism- Real and Imitation., Publication (Box 12, Folder 7)
- I.W.W. "More Truth About the I.W.W." Chicago: I.W.W., 1919. 47 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Industry and Fraternity. Address by Sidney Strong., 1917; Publication (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Author: Sidney Strong
- I.W.W. "On the Firing Line." Spokane, Washington: The Industrial Workers, 1912. 46 pages, Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: The Lumber Industry and Its Workers., Publication (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Notes: Third edition
- I.W.W. "One Big Union." Chicago: I.W.W., no date, 26 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: More Power to You., Publication (Box 12, Folder 10)
- I.W.W. "One Big Union of ALL the Workers: The I.W.W." Chicago, no date, 31 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: More Truth About the I.W.W., 1919; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: More Truth About the I.W.W., 1919; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
- I.W.W. "One Big Union of All the Workers; I.W.W." Chicago, 1933. 16 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: On The Firing Line., 1912; Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: On The Firing Line., 1912; Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
- I.W.W. "One Big Union of All the Workers." Chicago, no date. 31 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: One Big Union., Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: One Big Union., Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
- I.W.W. "One Big Union of the I.W.W." Chicago: 4th edition, 1944. 32 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: One Big Union of All the Workers; The I.W.W., Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: One Big Union of All the Workers; The I.W.W., Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
- I.W.W. "Opening Statement of George F. Vanderveer in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. William D. Haywood, et al." Chicago: I.W.W. Publishing Bureau, 1918. 102 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: One Big Union of All the Workers: I.W.W., 1933; Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: One Big Union of All the Workers: The Industrial Workers of the World, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: One Big Union of All the Workers: The Industrial Workers of the World, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
- I.W.W. "The Pageant of the Paterson Strike Performed by the Strikers Themselves." New York: The Success Press, 1913. 31 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: One Big Union of the I.W.W., 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fourth edition, Revised
  - Item 2: One Big Union of the I.W.W., 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fourth edition, Revised. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: One Big Union of the I.W.W., 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fourth edition, Revised. Copy 3.
  - Item 4: One Big Union of the I.W.W., 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fourth edition, Revised. Copy 4.
  - Item 5: One Big Union of the I.W.W., 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fourth edition, Revised. Copy 5.
  - Item 6: One Big Union of the I.W.W., 1944; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Notes: Fourth edition, Revised. Copy 6.
- I.W.W. "A Plain Statement of Its Structures and Principles." Chicago: I.W.W. 1934, 40 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Opening Statement of George F. Vanderveer in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. William D. Haywood, et al., 1918; Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Author: George F. Vanderveer
  - Item 2: Opening Statement of George F. Vanderveer in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. William D. Haywood, et al., 1918; Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Opening Statement of George F. Vanderveer in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. William D. Haywood, et al., 1918; Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
- I.W.W. "Que es la I.W.W.?" Una Sencilla Exposicion de Sus Principios, Objetos y Metodos." Chicago: I.W.W., no date. 32 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: The Pageant of the Paterson Strike Performed by the Strikers Themselves., 1913; Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
- I.W.W. "The Revolutionary I.W.W." Chicago: I.W.W., no date. 15 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: A Plain Statement of Its Structure and Principles., 1934; Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
- I.W.W. "The Silent Defense. A Story of the Remarkable Trial of Members of the Industrial Workers of the World held at Sacramento, Calif." Chicago: I.W.W., no date, 47 pages., Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Que es la I.W.W.? Una Sencilla Exposicion de Sus Principios, Objetos y Metodos., Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Language: Spanish.
- I.W.W. "The Truth About the I.W.W." Chicago, no date. 16 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Truth About the I.W.W., Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: Harold Callender
- I.W.W. "Twenty Five Years of Industrial Unionism." Chicago: I.W.W., 1930. 79 pages, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Twenty Five Years of Industrial Unionism., 1930; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Twenty Five Years of Industrial Unionism., 1930; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Twenty Five Years of Industrial Unionism., 1930; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
- I.W.W. "Unemployment and the Machine." Chicago: 1934? 48 pages, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  1934?
  - Item 1: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Notes: Copy 7.
  - Item 8: Unemployment and the Machine., 1934; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Notes: Copy 8.
- I.W.W. "What is the I.W.W.? A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods." Chicago: I.W.W., no date. 28 pages. (3rd revised edition and 2nd edition), Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: What Is the I.W.W.? A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods., Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: What Is the I.W.W.? A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods., Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: What Is the I.W.W.? A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods., Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: What Is the I.W.W.? A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods., Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Notes: Third edition, Revised
  - Item 5: What Is the I.W.W.? A Candid Statement of Its Principles, Objects and Methods., Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Notes: Third edition, Revised. Copy 2.
- I.W.W. Building Construction Workers. "A Handbook of the Industry." Chicago: I.W.W., 1923. 38 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Building Construction Workers. A Handbook of the Industry., 1923; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
- I.W.W. Bureau of Industrial Research. "Agriculture: The Worlds Basic Industry and Its Workers." Chicago: I.W.W., no date. 64 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Where Do We Go From Here?, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Notes: Chicago Branch No. 1, General Recruiting Union.
- I.W.W. Chicago Branch Number 1, General Recruiting Union. "Where Do We Go From Here?" Chicago, I.W.W., no date. 7 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Coal Mines and Coal Miners., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Coal Mines and Coal Miners., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Coal Mines and Coal Miners., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
- I.W.W. Coal Miners of the World. "Coal Mines and Coal Miners." I.W.W. Education Bureau, 1922. 108 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Educational Bureau. Historical Catechnism of American Unionism., 1923; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Educational Bureau. Historical Catechnism of American Unionism., 1923; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Educational Bureau. Historical Catechnism of American Unionism., 1923; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
- I.W.W. Department of Education. "Agricultural Workers Industrial Union, Number 110. An Economic Interpretation of the Job." Chicago: I.W.W., 1922. 61 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
  Missing; Also missing: I.W.W. Department of Education. "What is the I.W.W. Preamble." 1922. 40 pages.
  - Item 1: General Construction Workers: Builders of America., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
- I.W.W. Educational Bureau. "Historical Catechism of American Unionism." Chicago: I.W.W. Educational Bureau, 1923. 95 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: An Open Letter to President Harding From 52 Members of the I.W.W. In Leavenworth Penitentiary Who Refuse to Apply For Individual Clemency., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Author: I.W.W. (Industrial Workers of the World) General Defense Committee.
  - Item 2: An Open Letter to President Harding From 52 Members of the I.W.W. In Leavenworth Penitentiary Who Refuse to Apply For Individual Clemency., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: An Open Letter to President Harding From 52 Members of the I.W.W. In Leavenworth Penitentiary Who Refuse to Apply For Individual Clemency., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: An Open Letter to President Harding From 52 Members of the I.W.W. In Leavenworth Penitentiary Who Refuse to Apply For Individual Clemency., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: An Open Letter to President Harding From 52 Members of the I.W.W. In Leavenworth Penitentiary Who Refuse to Apply For Individual Clemency., 1922; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
- I.W.W. General Construction Workers. "General Construction Workers - Builders of America." Chicago: I.W.W. General Construction Workers, 1922. 22 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: California the Beautiful and Damned., Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "An Open Letter to President Harding from 52 Members of the I.W.W. In Leavenworth Penitentiary Who Refuse to Apply For Individual Clemency." Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, 1922. 28 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Eight Men Buried Alive: The Centralia Case Calls to Every Decent Man and Woman in the State of Washington to Act Quickly., 1924; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: Eight Men Buried Alive: The Centralia Case Calls to Every Decent Man and Woman in the State of Washington to Act Quickly., 1924; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: Eight Men Buried Alive: The Centralia Case Calls to Every Decent Man and Woman in the State of Washington to Act Quickly., 1924; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Eight Men Buried Alive: The Centralia Case Calls to Every Decent Man and Woman in the State of Washington to Act Quickly., 1924; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "California the Beautiful and Damned." Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, no date. 31 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 13)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "Eight Men Buried Alive: The Centralia Case Calls to Every Decent Man and Woman in the State of Washington to Act Quickly." Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, 1924. 31 pages., Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "Evidence and Cross-Examination of J.T. (Red) Doran in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. Wm. D. Haywood et al." Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, 1918. 151 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Evidence and Cross-Examination of J.T. (Red) Doran in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. Wm. D. Haywood et al., 1918; Publication (Box 14, Folder 1)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "Evidence and Cross-Examination of William D. Haywood in the Case of the U.S.A. vs. Haywood, et al." Chicago: General Defense Committee, no date. 312 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Evidence and Cross-Examination of William D. Haywood In the Case of the U.S.A. vs. Haywood, et al., 1918; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Evidence and Cross-Examination of William D. Haywood In the Case of the U.S.A. vs. Haywood, et al., 1918; Publication (Box 14, Folder 2)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "Public Opinion, Where Does it Stand on the Question of Amnesty of Political Prisoners?" Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, 1923. 32 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Public Opinion, Where Does It Stand On the Question of Amnesty of Political Prisoners?, 1923; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Public Opinion, Where Does It Stand On the Question of Amnesty of Political Prisoners?, 1923; Publication (Box 14, Folder 3)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "These are the Facts!" Chicago: General Defense Committee, no date. 16 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: These Are the Facts!, Publication (Box 14, Folder 4)
- General Defense Committee. "While Mr. Harding Reviews the Cases of the Politicals, Some Comment for the American People to Think About." Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, no date. 8 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: While Mr. Harding Reviews the Cases of the Politicals, Some Comment for the American People to Think About., Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: While Mr. Harding Reviews the Cases of the Politicals, Some Comment for the American People to Think About., Publication (Box 14, Folder 5)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. "Will You Help Now?" Chicago: I.W.W. General Defense Committee, 1912. 1 page., Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Will You Help Now?, 1913; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Will You Help Now?, 1913; Publication (Box 14, Folder 6)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. California Branch. "An Open Letter from the I.W.W. to the State's Attorneys of California." San Francisco: General Defense Committee, 1924. 14 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: An Open Letter from the I.W.W. to the State's Attorneys of California., 1924; Publication (Box 14, Folder 7)
- I.W.W. General Defense Committee. California Branch. "To the Beasts - in California as in Ancient Rome." I.W.W. General Defense Committee, 1924. 32 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: To The Beasts: in California as in Ancient Rome., 1924; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: To The Beasts: in California as in Ancient Rome., 1924; Publication (Box 14, Folder 8)
- I.W.W. General Recruiting Union. "Direct Action." Chicago, 1916? 20 pages, Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
  1916?
  - Item 1: Direct Action., 1916; Publication (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Author: I.W.W. (Industrial Workers of the World) General Recruiting Union.
- I.W.W. New York Defense Committee. "The Persecution of the Radical Labor Movement in the U.S." New York, 1919. 8 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Persecution of the Radical Labor Movement in the U.S., 1919; Publication (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Author: I.W.W. (Industrial Workers of the World) New York Defense Committee.
- I.W.W. Marine Transport Workers Industrial Union Number 510. "Exposed." Chicago: I.W.W., 28 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Exposed., Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Author: Marine Transport Workers Industrial Union No. 510.
  - Item 2: Exposed., Publication (Box 14, Folder 11)
- I.W.W. Railroad Workers Industrial Union. "A Union For All Railroad Workers." Chicago: I.W.W. 1948-1949 32 pages. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: A Union For All Railroad Workers., Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: A Union For All Railroad Workers., Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 3: A Union For All Railroad Workers., Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: A Union For All Railroad Workers., Publication (Box 14, Folder 12)
- I.W.W. Seattle Joint Branches. "The I.W.W." Seattle, no date. 8 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: The I.W.W., Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: The I.W.W., Publication (Box 14, Folder 13)
- "'Jersey Justice' at Work: First Decision on the Advocacy of Sabotage in the United States Courts." New York, 1913. 12 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: "Jersey Justice" at Work: First Decision on the Advocacy of Sabotage in the United States Courts., 1913; Publication (Box 14, Folder 14)
- "The 'Knights of Liberty' Mob and the I.W.W. Prisoners at Tulsa, Oklahoma." New York: National Civil Liberties Bureau, 1918. 16 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: The "Knights of Liberty" Mob and the I.W.W. Prisoners at Tulsa, Okla., 1918; Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Author: National Civil Liberties Bureau
  - Item 2: The "Knights of Liberty" Mob and the I.W.W. Prisoners at Tulsa, Okla., 1918; Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Item 3: The "Knights of Liberty" Mob and the I.W.W. Prisoners at Tulsa, Okla., 1918; Publication (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Koettgen, Ewald. "One Big Union in the Textile Industry." Cleveland: I.W.W. Publishing Bureau, no date. 14 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: One Big Union In the Textile Industry., Publication (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Author: Ewald Koettgen
- Korinsky, Philip. "Industrial Unionism and Revolution." New York: The Modern Press, no date. 47 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Industrial Unionism and Revolution., Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Author: Philip Kurinsky
  - Item 2: Industrial Unionism and Revolution., Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Item 3: Industrial Unionism and Revolution., Publication (Box 14, Folder 17)
- "Labor Scrapbook, the New Ear, the I.W.W. Trial, A Second Runnymede." Chicago: Charles H. Kerr and Company, no date. 31 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Labor Scrapbook, the New Era, The I.W.W. Trial, A Second Runnymede., Publication (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Lewis, Austin. "Proletarian and Petit-Bourgeois." Chicago: I.W.W. Publishing Bureau, no date. 47 pages. And Russell, Charles Edward. "What Comes of Playing the Game." 13 pages and Nearing, Scott. "Those Who Own and Those Who Work." 14 pages., Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Proletarian and Petit-Bourgeois., Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Author: AustinLewis
    Notes: 32 pages.
  - Item 2: Proletarian and Petit-Bourgeois., Publication (Box 14, Folder 19)